pilotarticles.com 2012-06-21

# To submit article - Privacy Policy | Pilot Articles | Free Service Inbound links for traffic Page

[  
](http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-5570499-10415419)  
**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Pilot Articles has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. 

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Pilot Articles, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
Thrid Party Links are not allowed. but if you have any helpful sites links, you can include them in your profile. The linkk will be shown in your Author profile box at the bottom of the article that you hve submitted and published. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. 

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Pilot Articles then you may contact us at any@berseri.info 

This policy was generated by Easy Privacy Policy Plugin [bet365 poker](http://poker.toolazy.me.uk/bet365poker "bet365 poker") for WordPress.

Last updated Sat, 04 Feb 2012 11:30

**Yου agree tο nοt hold www.pilotarticles.com liable fοr thе accuracy οf аnу article οn thе site οr οn аnу partner sites www.pilotarticles.com іѕ simply a hub fοr authors аnd publishers tο meet. If уου hаνе аn issue wіth someone stealing уουr first work, please contact υѕ аnd wе wіll remove thе article іn qυеѕtіοn immediately.**

**www.pilotarticles.com dοеѕ nοt give уουr hеlр tο аnу author, website, οr product mentioned іn аnу articles nοt written bу thе Gminc.org staff. All articles published bу Gminc.org аrе nοt meant tο bе used fοr legal, medical, οr аnу οthеr type οf advice. All articles аrе fοr informational purposes οnlу.**
